<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Founderchats on startup.school.nz</title>
    <link>http://startup.school.nz/founderchat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Founderchats on startup.school.nz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 17:05:40 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://startup.school.nz/founderchat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>founder.chat</title>
      <link>http://startup.school.nz/founderchat/founderchat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 17:05:40 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://startup.school.nz/founderchat/founderchat/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Meet the people in your community that are founders or want to become founders
and get help from them and help them in return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;founder.chat&lt;/em&gt; is a weekly event that brings together doers that help each
other to grow more successful businesses. As a business owner it is often hard
to find good advice, founder.chat tries to address this. By meeting weekly (not
everyone needs to come weekly) we create a hub for people to exchange
experience about what worked for them and what did not. Over time we create a
very resilient community of doers that share success and failure and the
resulting learnings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;format&#34;&gt;Format&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1 minute tell the rest of the group who you are, what you currently work on
and what you currently struggle with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is important that you are brief, funny and engaging. You want others to help
you with your problems so think about the number one issue that currently holds
you back and share it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find problem groups that came up during the 1min intros and form groups around
these problem groups. In the group, discuss the issues and find possible
solutions for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use actual problems not hypothetical ones, sole problems for people in the
group, you&amp;rsquo;ve got an hour!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all the problem solving, socialise in a nearby pub, wind down, talk to
people. This is the time to share things you don&amp;rsquo;t feel comfortable sharing
with everyone, where you can pull someone aside and ask a more personal
question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also the time where you get to learn your peers better and strengthen
your community &amp;hellip; and invest a bit in the local pub.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>