<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deep_dives on startup.school.nz</title>
    <link>http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deep_dives on startup.school.nz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 17:51:28 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Dive Workshops</title>
      <link>http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 17:51:28 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/workshops/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;We have seen that even just one day a month where you work on your business
instead of in your business make a huge difference in long term success. We
provide a easy way to spend a day a month learning and applying learning to
your business with an affordable workshop program for you and your team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting in August 2016 we will run monthly deep dive workshops in Nelson where
we invite teams to spend one day improving their business in one key aspect.
The workshops will introduce simple tools to the whole group, teams then work
through them on the day, present their outcome to the rest of the teams and
then move on to the next tool. To get most out of the course we highly
recommend bringing your whole team as we have seen the best results if everyone
is involved and have structured the pricing accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Courses run every first Sunday of the month, start at 10am and will run through
to around 5pm with a short lunch break. Please bring some lunch as we will not
provide any catering. Wind down and social time after the workshop at a
suitable location (Pub).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event is free of charge and we encourage to bring your whole team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;upcoming-events&#34;&gt;upcoming events&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://startup.school.nz/blog/deep_dive_nelson_august&#34;&gt;Nelson - 7th August&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>