<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deep_dives on startup.school.nz</title>
    <link>http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deep_dives on startup.school.nz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 17:51:28 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Dive Workshops</title>
      <link>http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 17:51:28 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/workshops/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Starting in August 2016 we will run monthly deep dive workshops in Nelson where
we invite teams to spend one day improving their business in one aspect of the
Lean Canvas. The workshops will introduce simple tools for the teams to work
through on the day, present their outcome to the rest of the teams and then
move on to the next tool. We will work through 5-6 tools every workshop and
provide mentoring during the exercises. To get most out of the course we highly
recommend bringing your whole team as we have seen the best results if everyone
is involved and have structured the pricing accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Courses run every first Sunday of the month, start at 10am and will run through
to around 6pm, hosted at Innovate. Wind down and social time after the workshop
at a suitable location (Pub).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To get the most out of this you should have
– a business and a team
– experience with the lean canvas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price: $100NZD per team&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;august&#34;&gt;August&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first workshop in our series of deep dive workshops is around finding the
right customer segments. We will introduce tools that help you identify new
segments, get a deeper understanding of “good” vs “bad” segments and how to
identify suitable early adopter segments for your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The workshop will run on the 7th of August, 10 AM at Innovate.  Please mail
INFO@INNOVATENELSON.COM if you want to be part of this, places are limited so
make sure you get in soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>