<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>startup.school.nz</title>
    <link>http://startup.school.nz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on startup.school.nz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 19:02:14 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://startup.school.nz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://startup.school.nz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 19:02:14 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://startup.school.nz/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;startup.school.nz started out as a way to run workshops in the Nelson region
that give local founders access to tools, networks and experience. We believe
that building a strong founder fabric needs founders to invest back into that
fabric. We do that by getting experienced founders to run workshops for the
community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Community trainings are free of charge for the participants as long as they are
owner/operator companies, small teams up to 5 people. To finance this we also
run corporate trainings where we help major companies to get back into the
habit of innovating.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Dive Nelson - August</title>
      <link>http://startup.school.nz/blog/deep_dive_nelson_august/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 15:10:36 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://startup.school.nz/blog/deep_dive_nelson_august/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first workshop in our series of &lt;em&gt;Deep Dive&lt;/em&gt; workshops is a foundational one
where we explore the Golden Circle and the Business Model Canvas. We will keep
coming back to these so if you plan to invest one day a month to work on your
business in the coming months, then we highly recommend you come around for
this one as these key concepts set you up for a good start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to get some preparation before the workshop I highly recommend watching the following TED talk by Simon Sinek


    
        
    

    &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ted.com/talks/simon_sinek_how_great_leaders_inspire_action&#34; target=&#39;_blank&#39;&gt;How great leaders inspire action&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The workshop will run on the 7th of August, 10 AM at Innovate (NMIT G Block).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please sign up on Eventbrite for this event here: 

    
        
    

    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.eventbrite.com/e/deep-dive-workshop-customer-segmentation-tickets-26439913493?aff=website&#34; target=&#39;_blank&#39;&gt;Signup on Eventbrite&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More information about the &lt;em&gt;Deep Dive&lt;/em&gt; program is here: &lt;a href=&#34;http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/workshops&#34;&gt;Deep Dive Workshops&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Weekend Nelson 2016</title>
      <link>http://startup.school.nz/blog/startup_weekend_nelson_2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 17:54:45 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://startup.school.nz/blog/startup_weekend_nelson_2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Startup Weekend is always a crazy ride of emotions, intensive learning and lack
of sleep. The last Nelson one was no different and it was another incredible
experience for me. I have done more than 20 Startup Weekends by now and one
would think I get used to the awesome energy and enthusiasm but to be honest
every weekend is a new experience and every Startup Weekend I learn a lot from
all the people involved in making this event so awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a few new elements we tried out this time around, one was the
greeting part at the very start. At the He Tangata Weekend we had Jeremy Banks
to provide the cultural aspect of the weekend and he started out with everyone
getting a chance to say who they are, where they are from and why they are
here. We took that and were fortunate that Sacha MacDonald explained the idea
to us and started us off to an awesome weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few impressions of the weekend&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


    

    
    




    
    
        
    


    

    &lt;div class=&#34;box alt&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;row uniform&#34;&gt;
        
        
        
            
                &lt;div class=&#34;4u&#34;&gt;
            
            
        
            
                
                    
                    &lt;span class=&#34;image fit&#34;&gt;
                
            
            
        
            
                
                        &lt;img src=&#39;http://startup.school.nz/img/2016/07/swnsn2016_1.jpg&#39;
                            alt=&#34;intro round&#34; /&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                
                
            
            
        
            
                &lt;div class=&#34;4u&#34;&gt;
            
            
        
            
                
                    
                    &lt;span class=&#34;image fit&#34;&gt;
                
            
            
        
            
                
                        &lt;img src=&#39;http://startup.school.nz/img/2016/07/swnsn2016_2.jpg&#39;
                            alt=&#34;Innovate welcoming everyone&#34; /&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                
                
            
            
        
            
                &lt;div class=&#34;4u$&#34;&gt;
            
            
        
            
                
                    
                    &lt;span class=&#34;image fit&#34;&gt;
                
            
            
        
            
                
                        &lt;img src=&#39;http://startup.school.nz/img/2016/07/swnsn2016_3.jpg&#39;
                            alt=&#34;evening, day 1&#34; /&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                
                
            
            
        
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;





    

    
    




    
    
        
    


    

    &lt;div class=&#34;box alt&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;row uniform&#34;&gt;
        
        
        
            
                &lt;div class=&#34;4u&#34;&gt;
            
            
        
            
                
                    
                    &lt;span class=&#34;image fit&#34;&gt;
                
            
            
        
            
                
                        &lt;img src=&#39;http://startup.school.nz/img/2016/07/swnsn2016_4.jpg&#39;
                            alt=&#34;working hard&#34; /&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                
                
            
            
        
            
                &lt;div class=&#34;4u&#34;&gt;
            
            
        
            
                
                    
                    &lt;span class=&#34;image fit&#34;&gt;
                
            
            
        
            
                
                        &lt;img src=&#39;http://startup.school.nz/img/2016/07/swnsn2016_5.jpg&#39;
                            alt=&#34;products for kids are developed here&#34; /&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                
                
            
            
        
            
                &lt;div class=&#34;4u$&#34;&gt;
            
            
        
            
                
                    
                    &lt;span class=&#34;image fit&#34;&gt;
                
            
            
        
            
                
                        &lt;img src=&#39;http://startup.school.nz/img/2016/07/swnsn2016_6.jpg&#39;
                            alt=&#34;sticky notes everywhere ...&#34; /&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                
                
            
            
        
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pitches were amazing, it always blows me away how the teams progress from
the first 1 minute pitch on Friday, then the first pitch practice on Saturday
night, when most of them are grateful that there is one more day to work out
all those holes they just found in their business, to Sunday night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though everyone won lots on this weekend the judges decided that a novel
baby monitor from the NapNanny team was the standout. In fact, they have
already started their kickstarter campaign and plan to launch the device for
real - we will report progress here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Dive Workshops</title>
      <link>http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 17:51:28 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://startup.school.nz/deep_dive/workshops/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;We have seen that even just one day a month where you work on your business
instead of in your business make a huge difference in long term success. We
provide a easy way to spend a day a month learning and applying learning to
your business with an affordable workshop program for you and your team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting in August 2016 we will run monthly deep dive workshops in Nelson where
we invite teams to spend one day improving their business in one key aspect.
The workshops will introduce simple tools to the whole group, teams then work
through them on the day, present their outcome to the rest of the teams and
then move on to the next tool. To get most out of the course we highly
recommend bringing your whole team as we have seen the best results if everyone
is involved and have structured the pricing accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Courses run every first Sunday of the month, start at 10am and will run through
to around 5pm with a short lunch break. Please bring some lunch as we will not
provide any catering. Wind down and social time after the workshop at a
suitable location (Pub).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event is free of charge and we encourage to bring your whole team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;upcoming-events&#34;&gt;upcoming events&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://startup.school.nz/blog/deep_dive_nelson_august&#34;&gt;Nelson - 7th August&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>founder.chat</title>
      <link>http://startup.school.nz/founderchat/founderchat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 17:05:40 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://startup.school.nz/founderchat/founderchat/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Meet the people in your community that are founders or want to become founders
and get help from them and help them in return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;founder.chat&lt;/em&gt; is a weekly event that brings together doers that help each
other to grow more successful businesses. As a business owner it is often hard
to find good advice, founder.chat tries to address this. By meeting weekly (not
everyone needs to come weekly) we create a hub for people to exchange
experience about what worked for them and what did not. Over time we create a
very resilient community of doers that share success and failure and the
resulting learnings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;format&#34;&gt;Format&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1 minute tell the rest of the group who you are, what you currently work on
and what you currently struggle with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is important that you are brief, funny and engaging. You want others to help
you with your problems so think about the number one issue that currently holds
you back and share it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find problem groups that came up during the 1min intros and form groups around
these problem groups. In the group, discuss the issues and find possible
solutions for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use actual problems not hypothetical ones, sole problems for people in the
group, you&amp;rsquo;ve got an hour!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all the problem solving, socialise in a nearby pub, wind down, talk to
people. This is the time to share things you don&amp;rsquo;t feel comfortable sharing
with everyone, where you can pull someone aside and ask a more personal
question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also the time where you get to learn your peers better and strengthen
your community &amp;hellip; and invest a bit in the local pub.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>